{
  "type": "QuestionSets",
  "question_sets": [
    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Questions",
      "categories": [
        "Vocabulary"
      ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wie' to English",
          "answer": "How",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Was' to English",
          "answer": "What",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wann' to English",
          "answer": "When",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Warum' to English",
          "answer": "Why",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wer' to English",
          "answer": "Who",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wie geht's?' to English",
          "answer": "How is it going?",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Mir geht's gut' to English",
          "answer": "I'm doing well",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wie heißt du?' to English",
          "answer": "What is your name?",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Kennst du?' to English",
          "answer": "Do you know?",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'How' to German",
          "answer": "Wie",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'What' to German",
          "answer": "Was",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'When' to German",
          "answer": "Wann",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Why' to German",
          "answer": "Warum",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Who' to German",
          "answer": "Wer",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'How is it going?' to German",
          "answer": "Wie geht's?",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'I'm doing well' to German",
          "answer": "Mir geht's gut",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'What is your name?' to German",
          "answer": "Wie heißt du?",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Do you know?' to German",
          "answer": "Kennst du?",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    },



    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Places",
      "categories": ["Vocabulary"],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Das Cafe' to English",
          "answer": "The Cafe",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Die Kneipe' to English",
          "answer": "The Pub",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Das Restaurant' to English",
          "answer": "The Restaurant",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Das Stadium' to English",
          "answer": "The Stadium",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Der Sportplatz' to English",
          "answer": "The Sporting Grounds",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Der Laden' to English",
          "answer": "The Shop",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Das Geschäft' to English",
          "answer": "The Shop",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Der Strand' to English",
          "answer": "The Beach",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Der Wald' to English",
          "answer": "The Forest",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Die Berge' to English",
          "answer": "The Mountains",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Der Urlaub' to English",
          "answer": "The Vacation",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Das Kino' to English",
          "answer": "The Cinema",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Cafe' to German",
          "answer": "Das Cafe",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Pub' to German",
          "answer": "Die Kneipe",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Restaurant' to German",
          "answer": "Das Restaurant",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Stadium' to German",
          "answer": "Das Stadium",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Sporting Grounds' to German",
          "answer": "Der Sportplatz",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Shop' to German (starting with L)",
          "answer": "Der Laden",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Shop' to German (starting with G)",
          "answer": "Das Geschäft",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Beach' to German",
          "answer": "Der Strand",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Forest' to German",
          "answer": "Der Wald",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Mountains' to German",
          "answer": "Die Berge",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Vacation' to German",
          "answer": "Der Urlaub",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'The Cinema' to German",
          "answer": "Das Kino",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    },



    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Pronouns",
      "categories": [
        "Verbs",
        "Conjugation"
      ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Ich'",
          "answer": "I - First Person - Singular",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "You - Second Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Du'",
          "answer": "You - Second Person - Singular",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "You - Second Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Er'",
          "answer": "He - Third Person - Singular",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "You - Second Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Sie' (Singular)",
          "answer": "She - Third Person - Singular",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "You - Second Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Es'",
          "answer": "It - Third Person - Singular",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "You - Second Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Wir'",
          "answer": "We - First Person - Plural",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Ihr'",
          "answer": "You - Second Person - Plural",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "They - Third Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "MultiChoiceQuestion",
          "prompt": "Which pronoun is represented by 'Sie' (Plural)",
          "answer": "They - Third Person - Plural",
          "incorrect_answers": [
            "I - First Person - Singular",
            "You - Second Person - Singular",
            "He - Third Person - Singular",
            "She - Third Person - Singular",
            "It - Third Person - Singular",
            "We - First Person - Plural",
            "You - Second Person - Plural"
          ]
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'I - First Person - Singular'",
          "answer": "Ich",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'You - Second Person - Singular'",
          "answer": "Du",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'He - Third Person - Singular'",
          "answer": "Er",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'She - Third Person - Singular'",
          "answer": "Sie",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'It - Third Person - Singular'",
          "answer": "Es",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'We - First Person - Plural'",
          "answer": "Wir",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'You - Second Person - Plural'",
          "answer": "Ihr",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Spell the pronoun that represents 'They - Third Person - Plural'",
          "answer": "Sie",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    },



    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Regular Endings",
      "categories": [
        "Verbs",
        "Conjugation"
      ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the ending of regular conjugated verbs in **FIRST PERSON SINGULAR FORM**",
          "answer": "e",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the ending of regular conjugated verbs in **SECOND PERSON SINGULAR FORM**",
          "answer": "st",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the ending of regular conjugated verbs in **THIRD PERSON SINGULAR FORM**",
          "answer": "t",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the ending of regular conjugated verbs in **FIRST PERSON PLURAL FORM**",
          "answer": "en",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the ending of regular conjugated verbs in **SECOND PERSON PLURAL FORM**",
          "answer": "t",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the ending of regular conjugated verbs in **THIRD PERSON PLURAL FORM**",
          "answer": "en",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    },



    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Machen (to do)",
      "categories": [
        "Verbs",
        "Conjugation"
      ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the **INFINITIVE** version of 'to do' in German",
          "answer": "machen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'I do' to German",
          "answer": "Ich mache",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'You do' (Singular) to German",
          "answer": "Du machst",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'He do' to German",
          "answer": "Er macht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'She do' to German",
          "answer": "Sie macht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'It do' to German",
          "answer": "Es macht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'We do' to German",
          "answer": "Wir machen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'You do' (Plural) to German",
          "answer": "Ihr macht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'They do' to German",
          "answer": "Sie machen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Ich mache' to English",
          "answer": "I do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Du machst' to English",
          "answer": "You do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Er macht' to English",
          "answer": "He do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Sie macht' to English",
          "answer": "She do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Es macht' to English",
          "answer": "It do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wir machen' to English",
          "answer": "We do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Ihr macht' to English",
          "answer": "You do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Sie machen' to English",
          "answer": "They do",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    },



    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Gehen (Going)",
      "categories": [
        "Verbs",
        "Conjugation"
      ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the **INFINITIVE** version of 'going'",
          "answer": "gehen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'I am going' to German",
          "answer": "Ich gehe",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'You are going' (Singular) to German",
          "answer": "Du gehst",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'He is going' to German",
          "answer": "Er geht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'She is going' to German",
          "answer": "Sie geht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'It is going' to German",
          "answer": "Es geht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'We are going' to German",
          "answer": "Wir gehen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'You are going' (Plural) to German",
          "answer": "Ihr geht",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'They are going' to German",
          "answer": "Sie gehen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Ich gehe' to English",
          "answer": "I am going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Du gehst' to English",
          "answer": "You are going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Er geht' to English",
          "answer": "He is going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Sie geht' to English",
          "answer": "She is going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Es geht' to English",
          "answer": "It is going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wir gehen' to English",
          "answer": "We are going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Ihr geht' to English",
          "answer": "You are going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Sie gehen' to English",
          "answer": "They are going",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    },



    {
      "type": "QuestionSet",
      "name": "Schlafen (to sleep)",
      "categories": [
        "Verbs",
        "Conjugation"
      ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "What is the **INFINITIVE** version of 'sleeping'",
          "answer": "schlafen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'I am sleeping' to German",
          "answer": "Ich schlafe",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'You are sleeping' (Singular) to German",
          "answer": "Du schläfst",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'He is sleeping' to German",
          "answer": "Er schläft",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'She is sleeping' to German",
          "answer": "Sie schläft",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'It is sleeping' to German",
          "answer": "Es schläft",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'We are sleeping' to German",
          "answer": "Wir schlafen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'You are sleeping' (Plural) to German",
          "answer": "Ihr schlaft",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'They are sleeping' to German",
          "answer": "Sie schlafen",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },


        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Ich schlafe' to English",
          "answer": "I am sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Du schläfst' to English",
          "answer": "You are sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Er schläft' to English",
          "answer": "He is sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Sie schläft' to English",
          "answer": "She is sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Es schläft' to English",
          "answer": "It is sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Wir schlafen' to English",
          "answer": "We are sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Ihr schlaft' to English",
          "answer": "You are sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        },
        {
          "type": "FreeTextQuestion",
          "prompt": "Translate 'Sie schlafen' to English",
          "answer": "They are sleeping",
          "strictness": "strict"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}